var multipleChoice = [
    {
        question: "JavaScript is the programming language of the _____.",
        options: ["Desktop", "Mobile", "Web", "Server"],
        answer: "Web"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following statement(s) is true about JavaScript?",
        options: [
            "It is a scripting language used to make the website interactive",
            "It is an advanced version of Java for Desktop and Mobile application development",
            "It is a markup language of Java to develop the webpages",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        answer: "It is a scripting language used to make the website interactive"
    },
    {
        question: "Which symbol is used to separate JavaScript statements?",
        options: [
            "Comma (,)",
            "Colon (:)",
            "Hyphen (_)",
            "Semicolon (;)"
        ],
        answer: "Semicolon (;)"
    },
    {
        question: "JavaScript ignores?",
        options: [
            "newlines",
            "tabs",
            "spaces",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        answer: "All of the above"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the correct syntax to call an external JavaScript file in the current HTML document?",
        options: [
            "<script src=\"jsfile.js\"></script>",
            "<script href=\"jsfile.js\"></script>",
            "<import src=\"jsfile.js\"></import>",
            "<script link=\"jsfile.js\"></script>"
        ],
        answer: "<script src=\"jsfile.js\"></script>"
    },
    {
        question: "Which JavaScript method is used to access an HTML element by id?",
        options: [
            "getElementById()",
            "getElement(id)",
            "getElementById(id)",
            "elementById(id)"
        ],
        answer: "getElementById(id)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which JavaScript method is used to write into an alert box?",
        options: [
            "window.alertHTML()",
            "window.alert()",
            "window.alertBox()",
            "window.alertContent()"
        ],
        answer: "window.alert()"
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript, single line comment begins with ___?",
        options: [
            "#",
            "/*",
            "$",
            "//"
        ],
        answer: "//"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default value of an uninitialized variable?",
        options: [
            "0",
            "undefined",
            "null",
            "NaN"
        ],
        answer: "undefined"
    },
    {
        question: "JavaScript arrays are written with _____?",
        options: [
            "round brackets ()",
            "curly brackets {}",
            "double quotes \"\"",
            "square brackets []"
        ],
        answer: "square brackets []"
    }
]